Tim Lemke



Developer

(647) 231 1648 - tim@timlemke.ca - www.timlemke.ca

Full stack web developer living and working in Toronto ON. Kind, inclusive team player with over two years of professional experience. Creative thinker and problem solver. Lover of fine coffee, a good super hero movie and LEGO.

Experience

Developer

SeventyEight Digital Inc - (Toronto ON), 2018 - present

- o Developing web sites and web applications for numerous clients across many different industries.
- Working daily with HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, ¡Query, Bootstrap, Foundation for Sites, SCSS (Sass), Gulp, Webpack, Kentico CMS (Portal Engine and MVC Solutions), Wordpress, C#, ASP.NET, Web Forms and MVC, Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator, Git, GitHub, Bitbucket and Sourcetree, among other languages, tools and technologies.
- o Actively involved in all stages of development life cycle, including interfacing with clients and assisting in project management.

Junior Web Developer

Advanced Utility Systems Inc - (Toronto ON), 2017 - 2018

- Worked daily with HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, DotNetNuke, C#, ASP.NET, SVN and Jira. Also utlized web accessibility testing tools including JAWS, NVDA, ChromeVox, Compliance Sheriff and Siteimprove, among other languages, tools and technologies.
- o Worked alongside QA department to improve accessibility of current web application and ensure it meets current WCAG and AODA standards. Actively involved in accessibility testing, identifying and addressing issues.
- o Actively involved in the design of new Angular web application project, and in fixing cross browser compatibility issues of current web application.
- o Organized internal web accessibility training sessions for developers in an effort to create and maintain internal accessibility development standards.

Skills













































...and always learning more...

Education

CERTIFICATE IN FRONT END DEVELOPMENT: HackerYou College of Technology (2017) MASTER OF MUSIC, MUSIC PERFORMANCE, JAZZ GUITAR: University of Toronto (2014 - 2016)